

## CONTACT

https://github.com/nikelneel27



nikhilneelakantan27@gmail.com



+91 8553632007

## **SKILLS**

HTML CSS Javascript

SCSS

Bootstrap

Vue Js

React Js

Vuetify

Figma

Photoshop

**Appium** 

Selenium

## **EDUCATION**

## **BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING**

2009-2013

Computer Science Engineering -

**EPCET** 

Visvesvaraya Technological University

# NIKHIL NEELAKANTAN

Software Engineer https://nikhilneel.netlify.app/

## **ABOUT**

Software Engineer with 6 years of experience as a Senior SDET, venturing into Frontend Web Development.

#### **PROJECTS**

**Dunder Milf**: https://dunder-mil.netlify.app/

The purpose of this app helps the HR to build a detailed joining offer letter that would be given to the suitable candidate ie. Position offered, complete breakdown of salary details, benefits, equity.

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Java Script, Vue, Charts used- Echart

Pets Meet up: https://pets-meetup-vue.netlify.app/

This app was built to help pet parents create and register for any pet meet up that is available. It can also be used for conducting adoption drive for Animal shelters.

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Java Script, Vue, Vuetify

Image Search : https://image-search-unsplash-api.netlify.app/

This app helps in finding beautiful high resolution images you are searching for. Its similar to the unsplash website, which helps Photographers to showcase their work.

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Java Script, Vue, Bootstrap, Unsplash Apis

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### LEARN-ONLINE.ORG/

Software Intern | April 2021 - July 2021 | Bangalore

## RENTOMOJO

SDET | Nov 2017 - Feb 2021 | Bangalore

- Testing the web and mobile applications for quality assurance and converting test cases into Test scripts.
- Wrote test cases and test scripts from scratch.
- Handled projects individually.
- Leading meetings and working on Agile methodology.

#### **TESTYANTRA**

SDET | Apr 2016 - Nov 2017 | Bangalore

#### **CAPTERA SOLUTIONS**

QA engineer | Jan 2015 - Feb 2016 | Bangalore

#### **ITC INFOTECH**

Software engineer | Jan 2014 - Jan 2015 | Bangalore